Fujian cuisine, Buddha Jumping Over the Wall
Latest Hot Cantonese Cuisine
Crayfish came to Guangdong
Geoduck meets shrimp paste
Regardless of its origin and faction
Collect all the good cuisine
Transformation in fusion
Innovation in imitation
Cantonese cuisine has no boundaries
Eating is only three meals a day
But for the research of eating
Guangdong people doesn't only stay in Lingnan
And never stop learning
and trying from other cuisines
As long as it is good cuisine
it will be transformed according to its own taste
For Guangdong
eating has no boundaries
Have a look. What would you like to buy?
There is really great Buddha Jumping Over the Wall
These are all
made with dried seafood
Buddha Jumping over the Wall
is the No. 1 dish in Fujian
About its name
One explanation is that
it is a homonym for Fushouquan in the Fuzhou dialect
And there is another explanation
It has a rich smell and is very delicious
So there is this verse
After opening the jar, the delicious smell went far away
even the Buddha gave up meditation and jumped over the wall to taste it
This is an exaggerated metaphor
This hodgepodge, which can bring
monks back to the secular world
has been passed down to this day
It evolves to be rich or light, complex or simple
But usually it can't be without an important main raw material
Hey! Handsome!
Today's abalone is great
Usually the price of it is 7 yuan
But some discount today
If the well-known Buddha Jumping over the Wall
is to be placed on the dining table of ordinary people
the cost of its main ingredients must be reduced
Its first main ingredient, abalone
used to be a rare and high-grade ingredient
but now it is also available
in ordinary markets
It benefits from modern large-scale aquaculture
In November
the southern city just entered the autumn (Guangdong, Huilai)
Not far from the ancient fort in Jinghai Town
there is an abalone aquaculture farm
Workers are busy with working
Wash those membranes to be washed
Understand? -Okay
Now we are making preparations for cultivating fry of abalone
The better the preparation
the better they will grow later
Autumn is the season for abalone breeding
Sperm and eggs ejected from abalone
are artificially intervened through complex technology
The hatched abalone fry are smaller than dust
Chen Huasheng's aquaculture farm
is preparing for the arrival of
a new batch of abalone families
Why hasn't it arrived after so long?
It's almost two hours later
than the scheduled time with merchant
How about the abalone fry?
Chen Huasheng was a little nervous in his heart
Here they come!
70 bags of abalone fry should be put into 60 ponds
First bring the temperature in the bag
closer to that in the pool
Wait a while before pouring them in
The grey ones are abalone eggs
There are about 200,000 in one pool
Looking at the abalone fry suspended in the water
Chen Huasheng finally felt at ease
This is the asparagus
we use to feed the abalone
But the amount of asparagus
in each pool needs to be controlled
Just enough to eat
in one night
16 years of experience
make Chen Huasheng very familiar with abalone farming
He, who was in the electrical business before
felt very unfamiliar when he first started abalone farming
and made a few mistakes
Chen Huasheng gradually became
good at farming abalone by perseverance
I didn't know anything about technology back then
I farmed abalone during the day
and read at night
I became obsessed
Now there are more than 10,000 cubic meters of water in our farms
Abalone farming requires high water quality
Directly introduced seawater cannot keep them alive
Chen Huasheng has his own way
We dug two meters deep in the sand
Use a 12-inch plastic tube
wrapped with a 20-mesh to 40-mesh plastic mesh
The water is as clean as mineral water
and flow 24 hours a day
Chen Huasheng wants to challenge difficult and correct things
His hard work finally paid off
Now the farms
produce nearly 50 tons of finished abalone every year
There are also 30 million abalone fry
The efforts of many people like Chen Huasheng
have made fresh abalone affordable for ordinary people
Pan fry
Deep fry
Steam
Poach
Dry fry
Fry
Roast
No matter how you cook it, it's the protagonist at the table
(Fried Abalone Slices)
(Steamed Abalone)
Its fresh and delicious meat is always mouthwatering
Its freshness and deliciousness is always mouthwatering
Remove the internal organs of the abalone and cut out the pattern
Cut the prime pork belly into small pieces
Add the seasoning and simmer them until medium rare
Then add the abalone and simmer them
Two rich and delicious ingredients
finally meet
Their smell smells so rich and delicious
The pork belly melts in the mouth
(Abalone with Braised Pork)
Abalone becomes more delicious after absorbing oil
Time to eat!
Come on
Let's eat together! -Okay
This mood becomes very different
This is the gift of the sea
It is rare to have a few confidants and friends together
During the National Day holiday
Chen Huasheng feasts guests with abalone
They're very cheerful
Autumn is cool and windy
It's a great season for drying dried abalone
Chen Huasheng makes
a part of abalone
into dried abalone every year
We only pick
those fatty abalones to make dried abalone
They have to be turned over three or four times
a day to get an even drying
5kg of fresh abalone can only be made into 0.5kg of dried abalone
The dried dried abalone
is in good shape
Thick abalone appears translucent
Salt oozes
out of the surface over time
The middle is transparent and has a red heart in the middle
This kind of dried abalone
is the favorite of Guangdong people
Yuexiu, Guangzhou
Madam
Bye-bye
Zhang Zefeng
He has been trading dried abalone
on Yide Road, Guangzhou since 1989
Because he is very familiar with all kinds of dried abalone
he is nicknamed Abalone Feng by his friends
How to tell if an abalone
is made into dried abalone before or after mating?
It depends on its thickness
From its thickness
If it's thin
it's post-mating
This dried abalone looks like
it was made before mating
Although dried abalone is expensive
not everyone is able to
make it into a delicacy
This inspired Zhang Zefeng
I have a friend
who was given a box of abalone
but he doesn't know how to cook it
so it has been sitting idle in the shoe cabinet for a long time
So we made these dried abalone
into semi-finished products
which can be eaten after heating
Ready-to-eat products not only provide convenience for customers
but also broaden the sales of dried abalone
The most luxurious dish
made with dried abalone
is the classic famous dish
Buddha Jumping Over the Wall
Abalone
Trepang
Fish maw
Scallop
Dozens of main and auxiliary materials
The Hong Kong-style Buddha Jumping over the Wall
contains
chicken
pig trotters
pig skin
fish
pig bones
snail meat
chopped scallops
and chicken feet
Abalone in the middle
Continue to put a layer of pork
Add about 15kg of water
After 20 hours of simmering
there is more than 4kg of abalone soup
It takes a week
for these dried seafood to soak
Add our Abalone Soup to it
Just simmer for 20
to 30 minutes
Convenient and fast
After several hours of alternating fierce fire and slow fire
finally a Buddha Jumping Over the Wall was completed
The moment
the stewed Buddha Jumps over the Wall is opened
the rich and delicious smell
reaches our hearts directly
Dozens of ingredients are stewed in a jar
Various ingredients are soft but not rotten and penetrate each other
Pair it with a bowl of rice with abalone soup
The golden soup
flows down the hills of rice
The umami of seafood and the sweetness of rice are intertwined
It is especially suitable for cold winters
Let's taste Buddha Jumping over the Wall first
while it's still warm
The prestigious Buddha Jumps over the Wall
thus completed the transition
from Fujian to Guangdong
But the crayfish
with its teeth and claws was not changed
and it was directly served on the table
Guangning , Zhaoqing
Crayfish
I want a spicy crayfish
Summer
is the peak season
for the annual crayfish market
In the county seat of Guangning
some late-night snack stalls are crowded with customers
With its deliciousness
crayfish has become
a popular delicacy in the country in recent years
Gradually piled up into hill-shaped shells
which shows its deliciousness and everyone's love for it
Crayfish also known as Red Swamp Crayfish
They were brought to China around 1929
Most of the crayfish come from Hubei
But there are also local products in Zhaoqing, Guangdong
In August
Rice harvesting completed in Daxin Village
It becomes the job of Cheng Shile
and his mother to collect discarded straw
Cheng Shile
Well, this straw is the good thing
It can breed bacteria
that make crayfish grow faster
Cheng Shile learned
the technique of cultivating crayfish
by chance with a friend from Hubei
Due to the COVID-19 outbreak in 2020, business is difficult to do
So he gave up
the brake pad business he had been in
He went back to his hometown and rented a 6.5-acre fish pond
and since then he started his career in crayfish farming
This month is the breeding season for crayfish
Cheng Shile is very worried about the food of crayfish
Now is the time to breed crayfish fry
I wake up early every morning
and grind this soy milk
Because crayfish fry
can't eat pelleted feed yet
So I just grind some soy milk for them
to give them extra protein
Crayfish are larger shrimp
in freshwater
It has a 98% survival rate
Their diet is very mixed
Weeds
algae
insects
and animal carcasses
are all their food
Cheng Shile planted black algae
in the crayfish pond as their feed
I haven't taken care of it in a while
so now I'm going to fish out part of it
Otherwise, too many water plants
will make the crayfish hypoxia
It can cause mass death
Time flies
After about two months
the crayfish molted several times
When they weigh between 0.02 and 0.04 kg
they can be fished and sold
At dawn every day
Cheng Shile started his day's work
with a shrimp trap in the morning glow
These crayfish are huge
The water here is mountain spring water, and the scenery here is beautiful
The lungs of
our farmed crayfish are clean
Large crayfish is about 0.03 kg, and even more
Medium-sized crayfish is between 0.02-0.03 kg
The quality of the crayfish is good
so many people come to buy it
How much is your crayfish
28 yuan for medium size, 35 yuan for large size
Okay, thank you, Boss
Take care
Now about 40-50 kg of crayfish
can be caught every day
It sold out soon
Can't even satisfy the local market
Cheng Shile wants to increase production
but the area of ​​the pond for breeding is too small
Cheng Shile
I want to cooperate
with these villagers to use this paddy field
for the joint cultivation of rice and crayfish to achieve double profit
This is my test field
I planted lotus root in it and put in crayfish
At that time, we can see  is
how much the production of crayfish
Handling crayfish requires skill
Grab its tail and gently pull it away
The crayfish's intestines will be pulled out together
It has too much impurities in its gills and stomach
Let's use scissors to cut diagonally
Then cut another knife along the back of it
and the cleaning is done
Father who likes to be busy will come to help
when he is not farming
Ouch! It hurts
I'd bleed if I didn't have the gloves
Behind every busy new farmer
who returns to his hometown
there is always the help of his parents
Cheng Shile also studied cooking
for two years before raising crayfish
As long as he is free
the kitchen at home is his battlefield
When relatives and friends come to my house for meals
I cook all the dishes
The texture of lobster is relatively rough
so the cooking method is relatively simple and direct
Deep fry crayfish
Drain them while they are medium rare
Stir fry the ingredients in hot oil to create an enticing smell
Put a little water
and a bottle of beer
Put the crayfish in it
Put the Thirteen Spice in or some spicy ingredients
Boil it for 15 minutes
Serve them after mixing
Thirteen Spiced Crayfish
Its smell is very strong
Won't get tired of eating it often
Spicy Crayfish
It's spicy but not too hot
Very tasty and smells good
Garlic Crayfish
is a little easier to cook
Fry minced garlic in hot oil to make smell
Then put the fried crayfish in and cook together
Just wait until they're fully mixed
Garlic Crayfish
It smells lighter
The crayfish tasted fresh and sweet
Minced garlic adds
to its deliciousness
Come on. Time to eat
Do you want it?
Oh, where are my eggs?
In October
Just after this batch of crayfish sold out
Cheng Shile rented another 25 acres
of field in the neighboring village
Grow lotus root
and mix it with crayfish
Cheng Shile felt that
after setting goals
he should do everything in a down-to-earth way
and realize his dreams step by step
Tianhe, Guangzhou
The quiet morning light spreads across
every street and alley in Guangzhou
The city with a history of more than 2,000 years
is awakened by the traffic on the street
It's sleepy-eyed
welcoming a new day
Brother Hui, good morning!
Good morning
Huang Jinghui
is the manager of the Chinese restaurant
in Mandarin Oriental, Guangzhou
Although it is not yet the working time of the back kitchen
he came to the kitchen very early
to start a new day's work
I don't come here so early every day
Coming before working hours
is a pressure for subordinates
I thought of a few dishes last night
So I came here this morning to have a try
what about this dish
This is the stewed yellow croaker with beer and fish maw
First fry the yellow croaker to make an attractive smell
Pour in the beer while the fire is on
Slowly cook it on a slow fire, and finally open a strong fire to dry the soup
When Huang Jinghui was 16 years old
he came to Guangzhou from his hometown to study cooking
Through his persistence and hard work
In just 4 years
he went from a helper to a chef
Until now
he manages several restaurants
under Mandarin Oriental Guangzhou by himself
(Stewed yellow croaker with beer and fish maw)
He especially likes to design his own dishes
The biggest feature
of Cantonese cuisine
is to absorb the essence of other cuisines
learn their advantages
and integrate Chinese and Western cuisines
I have a good habit
It is to carry out SOP
for the new dishes developed
Coconut stewed fish maw
Because of the habit of lifelong learning
Jiang Restaurant
chaired by Huang Jinghui
has been awarded two Michelin stars for three consecutive years
Huang Jinghui has many friends
He often invites some confidants
to get together in the Suiji Yard
another restaurant he runs
And he will personally preside over the dishes to treat friends
To this end, he often goes out
to find fresh ingredients
Taishan County, Jiangmen City
Taishan's sea environment is excellent
It is the traditional production area of Taishan oysters
four famous oysters in Guangdong
From November to April of the next year
oysters are plump and tender
sweet and refreshing
Nutritious Taishan oysters have become
the first choice of ingredients
on Huang Jinghui's hidden menu
Taishan oysters
grow at the intersection of brackish and fresh water
The ecologically excellent shallow waters
create its outstanding quality
Wow, so plump
Beautiful
Wow, this oyster is really tender
This oyster can be made golden oyster
In the winter
The warm sun shines brightly, on a day when the breeze is gentle
It is a great time to dry golden oysters
Selection of high quality fresh oysters
While the surface of it is oxidized
it also removes some moisture
Its surface will have a
light brown copper color
This is the golden oyster
This is Taishan Golden Oyster
One day drying can remove about 50% of the moisture
Nutrients of sun-dried golden oysters
haven't been lost after boiling
But after drying
its taste and aroma became unique
They are rare and high-quality ingredients
Bro Hui
These are the golden oysters
So beautiful
and superior
It smells so good
Bro Zhang
I want this one
Give me 5 kilograms
OK
They are of good quality
Guangzhou Huangsha Aquatic Products Wholesale Market
Aquatic products from all over the world are brought together  here
Huang Jinghui decides
to buy some seafood that is rare in China
This geoduck looks good
Geoducks live in the sand
The tubes of geoducks are always big and fleshy
They taste very good
Geoducks look like trunks
Geoducks from cold water regions of North America
are fresh and sweet
This geoduck looks wonderful
The king of geoducks
Geoducks are generally eaten as sashimi
Today let's try another way
Thick-sliced Canadian Geoduck in Chicken Soup
Ground-up chicken boiled in water
Keep the soup only
Wash the geoduck and keep the tube only
Cut it into square thick blocks
Blanch them in boiling chicken soup for 10 seconds
Plate them together with shrimp sauce and cabbage mustard
Fresh and elegant
(Thick-sliced Canadian Geoduck in Chicken Soup)
The surface of geoduck is already blanched
but the inside is just out of raw
Crisp and sweet
Because of the shrimp paste
the umami of geoduck
has released to a greater extent
and the sweet after taste lasts long
Golden oysters
Black truffles
What will the taste be
if these two ingredients put together
This dish is a combination of
two top Chinese and Western ingredients
Fully integrated
Fry the golden oysters in oil first
then braise in abalone sauce
Served with soft-yolk dried abalones
The flavor of thick abalone sauce
mixed with the smell of golden oysters
After sprinkling with black truffles
wisps of strange scent
(Soft-yolk Abalones with Black truffles and Golden Oysters )
wafts into the nasal cavity
Cut green onions vertically, mix them with oil and seasoning
Fresh mantis shrimp
Keep the meat only
Wrapped with spring roll wrappers
Fry the shrimp meat until it's just out of raw
Then get Russian sturgeon caviar
paired with fried mantis shrimp
Caviar is slightly fishy and salty
It will burst in the mouth first
Then come the crispy fried shrimp crust
Bite deeper
it's the delicious mantis shrimp
Levels of taste
suddenly become clear
(Mantis Shrimp Rolls with Russian sturgeon caviar and Green Onions)
At weekends
Huang Jinghui
always invites friends to meet together
Thank you Mr. Huang
Wish you booming business
The aroma of black truffles rises in the air
Then the taste of abalone juice and golden oysters
become thicker
Satiate their senses
The pursuit of balance
between food and drink
is long-standing
Seafood ingredients are combined creatively
with beer
to enhance its umami
Blue-girl beer from Germany
is brewed in double temperature brewing process
of 11 degrees and 16 degrees
to wake up the breath of the wheat
It combined well with the rich taste
of the seafood
Drink to the last drop
OK, to the last drop
The Blue-girl beer is really good
Let's drink more
OK, come on
Pickled fish
It is a classic dish of Sichuan cuisine
Known for its unique cooking techniques
It is one of the pioneers that led Sichuan cuisine
to the world
After the pickled fish was introduced into Guangdong
It's popular everywhere
Every restaurant that has something to do with Sichuan cuisine
won't miss this dish
Cantonese who love to eat and study
continuously improve the pickled fish
Make it suitable for locals
who prefer slightly spicy taste
or make new choices
on the raw material
Hurry up
Uncle, how is his fish?
The fish is good
Don't shoot me
I'm afraid of being famous
I don't have that much fish to sell
The fish that hide in the mountains
which sellers are reluctant to advertise too much
are just ordinary herb carps
After special breeding method
by the local villagers
It became famous
and expensive
Maoming, Xinyi
Zhongyan Village in Hongguan Town
is surrounded by mountains
In this plain that is on halfway up the mountain
There are twenty or thirty families
From south to north, a mountain stream
meanders through the village
The mountain stream is gurgling slowly
Beside it
There are dozens of puddles
in different sizes
Like many balloons
interlock on a rope
Go to the vegetable garden? -Yes
Every morning
Villager Qiu Hongyun
comes to the pit next to his house
to check the herb carps in the pit
(Qiu Hongyun)
Every family here
has one or two of pits like this
They are used for fish farming
Through these fish are ordinary
After growing up
they are really worth something
We will keep a few
When family reunites on holiday
and when relatives and friends come
it's a popular dish
It's delicious no matter how to cook it
People dig pits in front of and behind houses to store water
The intention is for the convenience of production and life
Cantonese call it Danzai
In the Tang Dynasty, some people raised fish in the pit
They are called Danzai fish
Today, in rural families
People no longer use the water from Danzai
But the custom of raising fish in Danzai
has remained until now
Qiu Hongyun is the backup cadre in the village
His own work is still farming
In my house
I just dug a pit like this
In the direction of the stream
it's the water inlet
Then over there
On the other side of the fish pond
It's our drain
So we can keep
the water flowing
Mountain stream is clear
It flows all year round
A unique water environment is formed
Single species of fish is put in
So there is no outlier competition
and more time for them to live
The water is mountain spring water
The water temperature is low
So our fish
grow slower
Before and after the spring equinox
we put the fry
When they weigh 3.5 or 4 kilograms
they will grow faster
Because they have adapted to the environment
Sunset at the mountain top
seems to be earlier
Qiu Hongyun comes to the fish pond again
to mow the grass and feed the fish
This one I'm cutting
is called elephant grass here
Those sweet potato leaves
and the cassava leaves
and the weeds in the ground
we will feed the fish with them
Fish grow up under the nourishment of mountain spring water
are fat and fleshy
Tough and firm
Sweet and smooth
Crispy in the mouth
And it won't rot for being cooked a long time
No mud and fishy smell
It's the best choice
to entertain guests in local
Mid-Autumn Festival is approaching
sister who has been working outside came back home
So that sister can eat
long-lost hometown dish
Qiu Hongyun and his sister started fishing together
Wow
It weighs 3.5 or 4 kilograms
Cantonese table
stresses much on the matching of new and old
Choose the part of fish breast with the thickest grease
and the fewest bone spurs
Steamed with a kind of mustard green
Plump breast meat (mustard green steamed fish breast)
fulled the crispy mustard green with the grease
The scented fish
and the salty mustard green
enhances the fresh and sweet flavor of fish
Perfect combination
gluts everyone with delicacies
Brother is busy
Sister Qiu Yanhong came to help
I work in Guangzhou
I eat the pickled fish often
This fish in our hometown
are of good quality
If it is used to make the pickled fish
that must be delicious
Wash the pickled cabbage, and stir it to dry
Sliced fish thinly
Fish bones and fish heads are fried and then boiled in soup
Until the soup thickens
put the fish in and wait until it is eight mature
Dried Chinese peppers, fresh Chinese peppers and peppers quick fried in oil
Drizzle when it's hot
With the sound of the oil
the house is full of the smell
of the pickled fish
The pickled cabbage can whet the appetite
and aid digestion
Unlike being steamed (Pickled Fish)
the fish is crunchy and crispy
Time for dinner
At night
The moon shines
The family reunites
Eat home-grown fish
It's simple
but sweet and reassuring
Zhaoqing, Sihui
Master Luo
New year is coming soon
I hope the kitchen could come up with
a few dishes
that are suitable for people in Sihui
How about
Let's use ducks to make several dishes (Luo Weiguang)
to everyone
OK
There are many ways to cook ducks
Stewed Duck with Orange Peel
Boiled Salted Duck
Blazing Duck
And Eight-treasure Duck
When Luo Weiguang was in junior high school
he started to help
his father who is a village cook
Learn to cook for many years
His dishes
have local characteristics
Near the Spring Festival
He received the task
of launching some classic dishes
Although less than a month left
Luo Weiguang is confident
and has no worries
Sihui is a beautiful place
There are so many wonderful ingredients
I like cooking ducks
It's delicious for sure
Duck meat contains a variety of
essential elements of human body
It is also a tonic food for people
It's the main material of Luo Weiguang's dishes
this time
Luo Weiguang has been helping
his father hardly
for more than ten years
Besides learning to be a man
he also learned the unique cooking skills from his father
My father is a village cook
He cooks very well
Especially the Eight-treasure Duck cooked by him (Eight-treasure Duck)
It's awesome
I didn't learn other dishes well
But only this one
I grasped it
Eight-treasure Duck
is a famous dish
from Shanghai and Suzhou
Eight different ingredients
are stuffed into the duck's belly
Then it becomes a delicious dish
When a plump
Eight-treasure Duck is served
With the fragrant aroma
People cut the reddish-brown duck
and enjoy a moment of surprise like opening a blind box
The duck skin on the outside is crispy
and the duck meat is tender and refreshing
The food inside
after soaking with duck oil
become loose
salty and mellow
Take a bite
Happiness fulls over the body
Like the meaning of its name
Rich taste
The delicious Eight-treasure Duck has been passed down to today
and became a classic dish in different cuisines
It's better to do what you are familiar with rather than something unknown
Luo Weiguang starts right now
At break time
he goes to visit a duck farm
Hello, Boss
Hello
What kind of ducks are you raising
Muscovy ducks
How many do you have
One place
can hold 15,000 ducks
I only have 5,000
They can have more space
Good luck
Luo Weiguang found a duck farm
that meets his requirements
Muscovy duck is a kind of famous meat duck among ducks
Fat
muscular
and docile
The duck farm is surrounded by rivers and mountains
The owner Li Huihua is from Chongqing
He has raised ducks
for more than 30 years
The duck farming industry
is from our ancestors
I started raising ducks when I was 16 (Li Huihua)
Boss
Your ducks here
look so spirited
What's the secret?
Good environment
Good water
Then the ducks will be beautiful
Muscovy ducks should be raised for about 80 days before releasing
They eat grass
So they are of good quality
Has found ducks that match his requirements
Luo Weiguang starts immediately
to cook some dishes for everyone
Blazing Duck (Blazing Duck)
It's a Cantonese dish with heavy taste
Simple but delicious
"Blazing"
means to burn the oil first
then put the duck in
Slowly fry the duck with oil
until the skin turns golden
Then fry other ingredients
Put the fried whole duck in the pan
and braise for 30 minutes
Duck meat becomes firmer after frying
It won't be pulpy after braising
It still tastes chewy
When you take a bite
the aroma of meat fat
will fill the mouth
Boiled Salted Duck is another light
but tasty dish
Marinate the whole duck for a day
then steam for half an hour
Cantonese Boiled Salted Duck
has strong aroma (Boiled Salted Duck)
It tastes like salted and dried duck
But it's not that salty
On the contrary, it tastes more fresh
Eight-treasure Duck was introduced to Guangdong very early
After the improvement of many predecessors (Eight-treasure Duck)
It has also become a classic dish of Cantonese cuisine
Luo Weiguang's Eight-treasure Duck
is mainly inherited from his father
Meanwhile, he adds
something from himself
The most important thing about Eight-treasure Duck is
to take out bones of the whole duck
Duck wings have thin skin
Be careful
Don't break its skin
Here is the duck thigh bone
The duck meat here needs to be cleaned
Around duck butt
There are something smelly
Remember to remove it
This is the duck that just boned
It's boneless
It can hold water
That's a success
Get the seed of Job's tears
black rice
lotus seeds
dried oyster meat
roast pork
scallops
peanuts
dried mushrooms
soaked well
Then mix them and flavour
Tie a knot at the neck of the duck
Put it into hot water to simmer
Slightly fry the duck body
Add thick soy sauce
Boil for two and a half hours
The Eight-treasure Duck
Combines traditional techniques with nostalgic tastes
very well
The duck meat is soft and tender
The filling is fragrant and soft
Dipped in soup, it has a rich
and lasting taste
Come on everyone
Let's try
the new dish together
The Eight-treasure Duck tastes really wonderful
Pretty good
The appointed day has arrived
Luo Weiguang's Duck Series
are appreciated by everyone
Also let him get a better understanding
of his father's cooking skills
Local dished are full of ingredients
and all-inclusive
(Luo Weiguang)
Cooking is just like being a man
If you cook with sincerity
people will feel that
A kind of local food
benefits from
the openness and tolerance of this land
In the Cantonese cuisine system
Everywhere
The shadow of each version of the cuisine can be found
No matter what a man's background is
how many unexpected things will happen
Cantonese chefs learn from China and foreign countries
Regardless of faction
they are willing to learn everything
Cantonese cuisine has no boundaries